Section 1
CARL:
Hi, come and take a seat.
JULIE:
Thank you.
CARL:
My name's Carl Rogers and l'm one of the doctors here at the Total
Health Clinic.
So I understand this is your first visit to the clinic?
JULIE:
Yes, it is.
CARL:
OK, well I hope you'll be very happy with the service you receive here.
So if it's aright with you I'll take a few details to help me
give you the best possible service.
JULIE:
Sure.
CARL:
So can I check first of all that we have the correct personal details
for you?
So your full name is Julie Anne Garcia?
JULIE:
That's correct.
CARL:
Perfect.
And can I have a contact phone number?
JULIE:
It's 219 442 9785.
CARL:
OK,
and then can I just check that we have the correct date of birth?
JULIE:
October tenth, 1992.
CARL:
Oh, I actually have 1991, l'll just correct that now.
Right,
so that's all good.
Now I just need just a few more personal details...
do you have an occupation, either full-time or part-time?
JULIE:
Yes, I work full-time in Esterhazy's you know, the restaurant chain.
I started off as a waitress there a few years ago
and l'm a manager now.
CARL:
Oh I know them, yeah, they're down on 114th Street, aren't they?
JULIE:
That's right.
CARL:
Yeah, l've been there a few times.
I just love their salads.
JULIE:
That's good to hear.
CARL:
Right,
so one more thing I need to know before we talk about why you're
here, Julie,
and that's the name of your insurance company.
JULIE:
lt's Cawley Life Insurance,
that's C-A-W-L-E-Y.
CARL:
Excellent, thank you so much.
GARL:
Now Julie, let's look at how we can help you.
So tell me a little about what brought you here today.
JULIE:
Well, I've been getting a pain in my knee, the left one.
Not very serious at first,
but it's gotten worse,
so I thought I ought to see someone about it.
CARL:
That's certainly the right decision.
So how long have you been aware of this pain?
ls it just a few days,
or is it longer than that?
JULIE:
Longer.
lt's been worse for the last couple of days,
but it's three weeks since I first noticed it.
It came on quite gradually though,
so I kind of ignored it at first.
CARL:
And have you taken any medication yourself,
or treated it in anyway?
JULIE:
Yeah, l've been taking medication to deal with the pain, Tylenol,
and that works OK for a few hours.
But I don't like to keep taking it.
CARL:
OK.
And what about heat treatment?
Have you tried applying heat at all?
JULIE:
No,
but I have been using ice on it for the last few days.
CARL:
And does that seem to help the pain at all?
JULIE:
A little, yes.
CARL:
Good.
Now you look as if you're quite fit normally?
JULIE:
I am, yes.
CARL:
So do you do any sport on a regular basis?
JULIE:
Yes, I play a lot of tennis.
I belong to a club so I go there a lot.
I'm quite competitive so I enjoy that side of it as well as the
exercise.
But I haven't gone since this started.
CARL:
Sure.
And do you do any other types of exercise?
JULIE:
Yeah, I sometimes do a little swimming,
but usually just when I'm on vacation.
But normally I go running a few times a week, maybe three
or four times.
CARL:
Hmm.
So your legs are getting quite a pounding.
But you haven't had any problems up to now?
JULIE:
No, not with my legs.
I did have an accident last year when I slipped and hurt my shoulder,
but that's better now.
CARL:
Excellent.
And do you have any allergies?
JULIE:
No, none that I'm aware of.
CARL:
And do you take any medication on a regular basis?
JULIE:
Well, I take vitamins but that's all I'm generally very healthy.
CARL:
OK, well let's have a closer look and see what might be causing this
problem.
If you can just get up...